var questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which daedric prince's sphere of influence includes nightmares, psychological terror and torment, dreams, bringing evil omens, and stealing memories?",
    choiceA: 'Mehrunes Dagon',
    choiceB: 'Mephala',
    choiceC: 'Vaermina',
    choiceD: 'Clavicus Vile',
    correct: 'C'
  },
  {
    question:
      "If you've completed the Companions main quests, then you are cursed with :",
    choiceA: 'Vampirism',
    choiceB: 'Polio',
    choiceC: 'Lycanthropy',
    choiceD: 'Hanahaki Disease',
    correct: 'C'
  },
  {
    question: "What is life's greatest illusion?",
    choiceA: 'Silence',
    choiceB: 'Innocence',
    choiceC: 'Worthiness',
    choiceD: 'Sanguine',
    correct: 'B'
  },
  {
    question:
      "If you are a member of Mage's Guild, then you have been to _____.",
    choiceA: 'Winterhold',
    choiceB: 'Balmora',
    choiceC: 'Solitude',
    choiceD: 'Dawnstar',
    correct: 'A'
  },
  {
    question:
      'Over time, the _____ began to devolve into twisted, blinded creatures, becoming the degenerate race now known as the Falmer.',
    choiceA: 'Snow Elves',
    choiceB: 'High Elves',
    choiceC: 'Dwemer',
    choiceD: 'Ayleid',
    correct: 'A'
  },
  {
    question:
      'After completing "The House of Horrors", this soul trapping daedric artifact is awarded to the Dragonborn :',
    choiceA: 'Skull of Corruption',
    choiceB: 'Skyforge Steel',
    choiceC: 'Black Star',
    choiceD: 'Mace of Molag Bal',
    correct: 'D'
  },
  {
    question: '"Fus Ro Dah!" are the three words that form which Dragon Shout?',
    choiceA: 'Unrelenting Force',
    choiceB: 'Whirlwind Sprint',
    choiceC: 'Dragonrend',
    choiceD: 'Marked for Death',
    correct: 'A'
  },
  {
    question:
      "Featuring a civil war following a king's death, hostile undead warriors, the appearance of dragons, and a murderous wedding, Skyrim bares incredible similarities to which wildly popular HBO series?",
    choiceA: 'Outlander',
    choiceB: 'The Last Kingdom',
    choiceC: "Pete's Dragon",
    choiceD: 'Game of Thrones',
    correct: 'D'
  },
  {
    question:
      'The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim is heavily influenced by which polytheistic religion?',
    choiceA: 'Neopaganism',
    choiceB: 'Greek Mythology',
    choiceC: 'Old Norse',
    choiceD: 'Vedism',
    correct: 'C'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following cannot become a follower?',
    choiceA: 'A dog',
    choiceB: 'A Giant',
    choiceC: 'A riekling',
    choiceD: 'An armored troll',
    correct: 'B'
  }
]
